<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cow Horse And Buffalo</string>
    <string name="sapi_kuda_dan_kerbau_pedia">Cow Horse and Buffalo Pedia</string>
    <string name="tentang">About</string>
    <string name="notifikasi">press image to open gallery</string>
    <string name="ras_sapi">Cow Breed</string>
    <string name="jenis_hewan">Animal Type</string>
    <string name="asal">Address</string>
    <string name="deskripsi_hewan">Animal Description</string>
    <string name="nama">Name</string>
    <string name="nim">NIM</string>
    <string name="prodi">Study Program</string>
    <string name="sistem_informasi">Information System</string>
    <string name="semester">Semester</string>
    <string name="daftar_ras_hewan">List of Breeds</string>
    <string name="kuda_arab">arabian horse</string>
    <string name="arab">arab</string>
    <string name="holstein_nama">holstein</string>
    <string name="holstein_asal">europa</string>
    <string name="galloway_nama">galloway</string>
    <string name="galloway_asal">skotland</string>
    <string name="hereford_nama">hereford</string>
    <string name="cachena_nama">cachena</string>
    <string name="anggus_nama">anggus</string>
    <string name="arab_asal">arab</string>
    <string name="appoloosa_nama">appoloosa horse</string>
    <string name="appoloosa_asal">america</string>
    <string name="dutch_asal">netherland</string>
    <string name="mustang_nama">mustang horse</string>
    <string name="murrah_nama">murrah</string>
    <string name="murrah_asal">india</string>
    <string name="rawa_nama">rawa</string>
    <string name="rawa_asal">filiphina</string>
    <string name="mediterania_nama">mediterania</string>
    <string name="mediterania_asal">italy</string>
    <string name="nagfuri_nama">nagfuri</string>
    <string name="nagfuri_asal">india</string>
    <string name="surti_nama">surti</string>
    <string name="surti_asal">gujarat</string>
    <string name="galloway_deskripsi">The Galloway is one of the longest beef cattle breeds in the world, named after the Galloway region of Scotland, where it originated, in the 17th century.</string>
    <string name="hereford_asal">subtropical climate</string>
    <string name="hereford_deskripsi">Hereford cattle are a type of beef cattle originating from areas with a subtropical climate."</string>
    <string name="cachena_asal">portugal</string>
    <string name="cachena_deskripsi">Cachena is a dual purpose breed of cattle from Portugal and Galicia, Spain. In Portugal, there is also a similar but larger breed of cattle known as Barrosão or Barrosã</string>
    <string name="anggus_asal">scotland</string>
    <string name="anggus_deskripsi">The Aberdeen Angus, sometimes just Angus, is a small Scottish breed of beef cattle. It comes from native cattle from the counties of Aberdeen, Banff, Kincardine and Forfar in northeastern Scotland.</string>
    <string name="arab_nama">arabian horse</string>
    <string name="arab_deskripsi">a type of horse race originating from the Arab region, kept by people for various purposes. Because of its high posture, special performance, namely excellent body resistance, intelligence, agility, Arabian horses were also used for war.</string>
    <string name="appoloosa_deskripsi">The Appaloosa is an American horse breed that is best known for its colorful coat patterns. There is a wide variety of body types within the breed, stemming from the influence of several horse breeds throughout its history.</string>
    <string name="dutch_nama">Dutch warmblood horse</string>
    <string name="dutch_deskripsi">The Dutch Warmblood is a warm-blooded horse breed registered with the Koninklijk Warmbloed Paardenstamboek Nederland, which regulates the breeding of competition and jumping horses, as well as racehorses and racehorses.</string>
    <string name="mustang_asal">western united states "</string>
    <string name="mustang_deskripsi">The Mustang is a free-roaming horse in the Western United States, descended from horses brought to America by the Spanish. Mustang is often referred to as a wild horse </string>
    <string name="murrah_deskripsi">Murrah buffalo is a type of buffalo that is kept mainly for milk production. It originates from Haryana and Punjab in India </string>
    <string name="rawa_deskripsi">The Carabao is a domestic marsh-type buffalo native to the Philippines. Carabao was introduced to Guam from Spanish Philippines in the 17th century </string>
    <string name="mediterania_deskripsi">The Italian Mediterranean buffalo is a breed of Italian buffalo. This buffalo is a type of river buffalo and is similar to the type of buffalo in Hungary, Romania and the Balkan countries.</string>
    <string name="nagfuri_deskripsi">Nagpuri is a breed of buffalo that originates from Maharashtra, India. It stands out better among the buffalo breeds that combine milk quality and drought in better proportions under adverse climatic conditions. </string>
    <string name="surti_deskripsi">Surti is a breed of buffalo found in the Kaira and Vadodara districts of Gujarat between the Mahi and Sabarmati rivers. The average milk production is 1600–1800 liters</string>
    <string name="holstein_deskripsi">Holstein cow or Frisia is one of the dairy cattle breeds which is now known as the cow that produces the most milk in dairy farms. </string>
    <string name="sapi">Cow</string>
    <string name="kuda">Horse</string>
    <string name="kerbau">Buffalo</string>
    <string name="sapi_list_title">List of cow Breeds</string>
    <string name="kuda_list_title">List of Horse Breeds</string>
    <string name="kerbau_list_title">List of Buffallo Breeds</string>
    <string name="daftar_ras_judul">List of Breeds</string>
</resources>